quamut.com 2008-06-01

# Quamut: the go to how to

Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki respect your privacy and will do our best to earn and keep your trust. This Privacy Policy identifies how we collect, use and protect the personal information you provide to us when you visit the Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki websites. By using the Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki sites, you agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and related [Terms of Service](http://www.quamut.com/terms). 

**What Information Is Collected and How Is It Used?**

**a. Personal Information You Actively Submit to Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki.** You may choose to provide certain personal information to Quamut.com or Quamut Wiki through these sites. This "personal information" may include your name, billing address, shipping address(es), telephone number, email address, and credit card number. You may be asked to provide this information when you want to register for the websites, purchase printed or downloadable PDF formatted content, post to message boards, or contact us with a question or comment. To use all features of the Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki websites, you need to create a password-protected account with us. When you want to make a purchase or change your stored personal information, we approve your access by verifying your email address with your password. You can browse the Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki sites and read online content without having to submit personal information. 

We use the personal information described above to fulfill your orders, provide customer support, and communicate with you. In addition, Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki may use the information to market its products and services to you. When you register with Quamut.com or Quamut Wiki, you can choose whether you wish to receive marketing communications from us. 

Except as described below, Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki will not disclose your personal information to third parties who are not our affiliates without your consent. We do not sell or exchange customer lists or customer information for marketing purposes with unaffiliated third parties, and will not do so without your express permission. We may share anonymous, aggregate information concerning the demographic makeup of our customers to unrelated third parties. 

We may share personal information we collect for business purposes with companies and individuals who provide servicing, administrative, marketing, and other services for us, or on our behalf. Companies we hire to provide such services are only permitted, by contract, to use your information for the performance of the specific services we have requested of them, and are restricted from using such information in any way not expressly authorized by Quamut.com or Quamut Wiki. 

Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki may disclose personal information to government and regulatory authorities as permitted or required by applicable law, to enforce or apply the terms of any of our policies or user agreements, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Quamut.com, Quamut Wiki, our users, or others. 

Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites that may be linked to this site. When you click on links and banners on our sites that take you to third-party web sites, you will be subject to the third parties' privacy policies you are linking from our sites or browsing on your own. 

Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any personal information, photographs, video or other content that you may disclose publicly on any message board or similar public forum. Further, Quamut.com, Quamut Wiki and its affiliated entities assume no liability for any action of any third party who collects any information users may publicly disclose through such public forums. 

**b. Automatically Collected Information.** Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki use tracking software and similar technology, which automatically collects anonymous information about your computer hardware and software when you visit the Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki sites. We receive and collect the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, the browser software you use and your operating system, the date and time you access our sites, and the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our sites. We use this information to monitor the usage of our sites. Also, when we send emails to you, we may be able to identify information about your email address, such as whether you can read graphic-rich HTML emails. All of the information we automatically capture provides us with the ability to enhance our users' experience at Quamut.com or Quamut Wiki and to determine aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns. 

**c. Information Collected via Cookies.** Quamut.com, Quamut Wiki and its third party advertisers may use cookies to enhance your experience on the Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki sites. "Cookies" are small files or records that we place on your computer's hard drive to collect information about your activities on Quamut.com or the Qumaut Wiki site, and which allow us to better customize your visit to the sites. The information captured makes it possible for us (i) to speed navigation, keep track of your purchases, and provide you with custom tailored content; (ii) to remember information you gave to us so you don't have to reenter it each time you visit the Quamut.com or Quamut Wiki sites; (iii) to monitor the effectiveness of certain of our marketing email campaigns; (iv) to monitor total number of registered users and their associated demographic information, pages viewed, and the total number of banners served; and (v) to target advertising according to demographic information. 

Most people do not know that cookies are being placed on their computers when they visit most web sites because browsers are typically set to accept cookies. You can choose to have your browser warn you every time a cookie is being sent to you or you can turn off cookie placement. If you refuse cookies, however, you will not be able to complete an order with us online. Also, if you do not accept cookies, your overall Internet browsing experience will be affected. 

**d. Information Collected Using Pixel Tags or Clear GIFs.** To help us understand the effectiveness of certain of our email marketing efforts, Quamut.com or Quamut Wiki may use "message format" and "message open" sensing technologies. Both technologies require the use of pixel tags or clear GIFs (also called web beacons). The "message format" sensing technology allows us to recognize whether you have enabled your email program to receive HTML emails; if so, this information is then associated with your email address so that subsequent messages can be sent to you in HTML format. The "message open" sensing technology allows us to recognize whether you have opened our email message. We can only detect this if your have enabled your email program to receive HTML emails. 

**How Is Your Personal Information Protected?**

Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki maintains reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information, to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. Nonaffiliated third parties are contractually obligated to maintain strict confidentiality, and are not permitted to use your personal information for marketing purposes, or for any other purpose other than that we have requested of them. To further secure your personal information: 

**a.** We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology to prevent such information from being intercepted and read as it is transmitted over the Internet. The encrypted data goes to a secure site where your information is stored on restricted-access computers located at restricted-access sites. 

**b.** We require you to create a customer password when you establish an account with us. We encourage you to use a password that is not easily determinable (i.e., don't use your name or street name). Keep your password secure do not share it with anyone. 

When you want to make a purchase or change your stored personal information, we approve your access by verifying your email address with your password. 

If you forget your password, you can click [here](http://www.quamut.com/user/lost/) and request a new password. If you want to change your password or other account information, you can also do so [here](http://www.quamut.com/user/myquamut/). 

**c.** We encourage you to remember to log out. To prevent unauthorized access to your account, you should log out once you have (i) completed your transaction, (ii) completed managing your account, or (iii) decided to step away from your computer. Anyone who accesses your computer after you have signed in but before you have logged out can access your account.

While we will use such efforts described above, Quamut.com, Quamut Wiki and its affiliated entities assume no liability for any disclosure of personal information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control. 

**How Can You Access or Correct Your Personal Information?**

To access, correct or delete your personal information stored by Quamut.com, please click [here](http://www.quamut.com/user/myquamut/). 

**How Does This Privacy Policy Apply to International Users?**

The Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki websites are hosted on servers in the United States and all personal information collected by Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki from these websites will be collected, used and otherwise processed in the United States, including information voluntarily provided by users outside the United States. By accessing and using these websites, you consent to the use of your information in the United States in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**What About Children's Personal Information?**

Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki are not targeted to children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect contact information from them. Our products and services are marketed for purchase with the consent of adults or by adults. To protect the privacy of any user of our site who is under the age of 13, we do not permit them to post any contact information. 

**How Will You Know If We Change Our Privacy Policy?**

Quamut.com and Quamut Wiki reserve the right to modify or amend this policy at any time by posting the revised privacy policy on our site. The changes will only affect the information we collect after the effective date of the change to our privacy policy unless we clearly express otherwise. 

**If You Have Any Questions About This Privacy Policy:**

Please contact us at [privacy@quamut.com](mailto:privacy@quamut.com)   
For all other inquiries, please visit our [contact page](http://www.quamut.com/contact).
